## **David Medina**

## **Full stack Developer**

Over almost 2 years of professional experience developing all kinds of apps or web pages, from design in the front to develop full logic in the back end. I enjoy working in close collaboration with teams across technology, business and design.

mail

rafaelsanchez97.dm@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/david-medina-435a50199/Phone

+54 9 11 73698281

**Portfolio** 

https://portfolio-next-davidms5.vercel.app/

## Experience

## independent web developer

Nov 2021 - Present

Designing end-to-end apps and pages on web platforms. Working closely with clients, from companies to startups.

## web development project

Dall-e Blog Project . may 2022- jul 2022

the project was made using the MERN stack, to connect with the Dall-e API to generate images with AI. making a Blog to show and download the images generated by the people who access to it

link: https://ai-images-app-blog.vercel.app/

## front End developer and designer

ChatGPT Blog, Dec 2021 - Mar 2022

Redesigned a Blog's homepage with a modern design oriented to the new technologies like ChatGPT and artificial intelligence; increased traffic in the site by 35%

link to the design: davidms5.github.io/GPTCHAT-webpage/

## **Skills**

#### FRONT END AND DESIGN:

ReactJS, NextJS, Redux & Redux Toolkit, Styled-components, Tailwind CSS, Figma

#### **BACK END:**

,Typescript, NodeJS, Express, Python, Django, MongoDB, PostgreSQL

#### misc:

Experienced with SCRUM, Agile & Lean methodologies. English C1, Spanish, French, currently learning Japanese

## **Education & Learning**

## **Full Stack Web Developer**

SoyHenry Bootcamp, 2023

#### React + Redux

SoloLearn. Dec 2022

### **JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures**

FreeCodeCamp, Mar 2021

# higher university technician in electromedicine

experimental national University "Francisco de Miranda", 2013 – 2018

#### **Hobbies**

Read books: Science, Philosofy, chemistry and others learn new languages besides programming ones, videogames, archery, snowboading